applytoeducation.com 2008-12-17

# Privacy Pledge

**Privacy Policy**

We work hard to secure the **_apply_** to **education** website in order to protect your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how personal information from you or about you may be received or collected by us, and is used or disclosed as a consequence of your activities on this site. 

**_apply_** to **education** is web based software that enables teachers, administration & support applicants (“applicants”) to search job postings free of charge, e-file one comprehensive application portfolio and e-courier their application portfolio to multiple jobs posted by multiple School Boards and Private Employers (“employers”) on **_apply_** to **education**. Employers can post job openings on **_apply_** to **education** and search applicants who have given them permission to view their application. Applicants have the choice of joining or visiting **_apply_** to **education**. Under either option, they can view School Boards’ job postings free of charge. Any person who visits **_apply_** to **education** is considered a “user” of **_apply_** to **education**.

By accessing, using and/or downloading materials from or sending and posting materials to **_apply_** to **education** , you are agreeing, on your own behalf, and as agent on behalf of any other person or entity who you represent, to the terms of this Privacy Policy and to the methods and the Terms of Use attached hereto for the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information as described here. Please review the Terms of Use before proceeding further. 

Our site contains links to other Web sites over which we have no control. **_apply_** to **education** is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of other Web sites you choose to visit through **_apply_** to **education**. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those Web sites so you understand how they collect, use and share your information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to the information we collect on **_apply_** to **education**. 

The **_apply_** to **education** website, its technical components (including the servers hosting the website), and **_apply_** to **education** ’s employees are all located within Canada and adhere to Canadian privacy laws. 

**Your Information**

In some areas of our Web site, **_apply_** to **education** requests or may request applicants to provide specific personal information, including: name, address, email address, telephone number, qualifications, experiences, education, resume, cover letter, supporting documents, credit card number, and any other information from which identity is evident or may be verified. In other areas, **_apply_** to **education** collects or may collect general information that is not unique such as Province, City and ZIP code. Sometimes we collect or may collect a combination of the two types of information. Examples of areas on **_apply_** to **education** where we collect personal or combined personal and general data are pages where you can open an account or fill out your application. 

We may also gather certain information about the use of our site, for example, information about which areas are visited and the services accessed. Moreover, there is information about users’ computer hardware and software that is or may be collected by **_apply_** to **education**. This information can include without limitation; IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. 

Applicants may correct or update their **_apply_** to **education** application at any time. Moreover, applicants can make their application not visible to our online database at any time. In the event an application expires or is made not visible, we maintain an archival copy that will be accessible only by the applicant. If applicants mail us documents to scan and upload to their application we will store their documents for 30 days after scanning them and then shred them. 

**What We Do With Your Information**

The information we gather on **_apply_** to **education** is used for the limited purpose of allowing applicants to search for jobs and e-courier their application to employers on **_apply_** to **education** . Applicants select the employers they want to e-courier their information to. Only those employers who are selected by an applicant are given access to his/her information. General non-personal information and technical information is used for the purpose of operating and improving the site. We may use contact information for the limited purpose of sending email, mail, or other communications with respect to the status of an applicant’s account or any technical issues that arise relating to the use of the site by an applicant. 

Applicants may consent to receive email updates on **_apply_** to **education** , such as “job alerts” regarding recent job postings that match criteria the applicant selected or features in the application. The nature and frequency of these messages will vary. An applicant who has consented to receive email updates may update their portfolio and remove their consent at any time. 

**_apply_** to **education** is a division of Passion Inc. Personal information collected by **_apply_** to **education** is not used by Passion Inc. for any other purpose other than the purposes described above. Personal information is not shared between divisions of Passion Inc. Should Passion Inc. wish to use the personal information of an **_apply_** to **education** user, for any other purpose than as previously stated, Passion Inc. will ask for further consent from that user for the specific use of that information. That request and consent will be explicit. This privacy policy and the use of the **_apply_** to **education** website do not constitute further consent to use.

**_apply_** to **education** allows you to submit feedback. Should you choose to submit feedback, you are consenting to our contacting you by way of follow-up email or phone call to discuss your feedback. We may also ask for your permission to use your feedback for marketing purposes. 

We do not disclose your personal information, combined personal and demographic information or information about your use of **_apply_** to **education** (such as the areas you visit or the services you access) to third parties, except as set forth in the following three subparagraphs. 

  1. We may disclose such information only as is necessary to third parties who are employed by us or retained by us by contract to perform functions on our behalf, including the hosting of web servers, processing credit card transactions and providing customer service. The employees and independent contractors employed by us are governed by the privacy laws of Canada and by **_apply_** to **education** ’s privacy policy. 
  2. We may disclose such information if legally required to do so, if requested to do so by a governmental entity or if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary to: conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process; protect the rights or property of **_apply_** to **education** ; prevent a crime or protect national security; or protect the personal safety of applicants or the public. 
  3. We may disclose and transfer such information to a third party who acquires all or a substantial portion of **_apply_** to **education** 's business, whether such acquisition is by way of merger, consolidation or purchase of all or a substantial portion of our assets. In addition, in the event **_apply_** to **education** becomes the subject of a bankruptcy proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, **_apply_** to **education** or its trustee in bankruptcy may sell, license or otherwise dispose of such information in a transaction approved by the bankruptcy court. 

**_apply_** to **education** may also share collected anonymous information about visitors to our site (for example, the number of visitors per month) with its clients, partners and other third parties so they understand the kinds of visitors to **_apply_** to **education** and the use of the site. 

**_apply_** to **education** supplies technology, hosting, and related services to employers to help them manage applications on-line. Personal and/or general information supplied by an applicant becomes part of the **_apply_** to **education** database, but it is not accessible by anyone other than the applicant, **_apply_** to **education** , and the employer(s) selected by the applicant to view his/her application or by the employers whose jobs the applicant applies to. 

**Applications**

**_apply_** to **education** is a web-based software that enables applicants to search job postings free of charge, e-file one comprehensive application portfolio and e-courier their application portfolio to multiple jobs posted by multiple employers on **_apply_** to **education** . In addition to the provisions of this Privacy Policy, the collection, use and distribution of the application is governed by the Terms of Use. There are two options available to applicants once their application is submitted into our on-line database and has an ‘Active’ credit: 

  1. The application can be stored in our database and set to ‘not visible’ by the applicant so it is not searchable by School Boards and/or Private Employers. Not allowing the application to be searchable means it can be used to apply for a job online, but School Boards and Private Employers will not have access to search it through our application database. 
  2. The application can be stored in our database and set to ‘visible’ by the applicant so it can be viewed by employers the applicant has selected and by employers whose job postings the applicant has applied to.

We limit access to our searchable application database (or copies thereof) to School Boards and Private Employers. Once an applicant has made his/her application available to employers through **_apply_** to **education** , **_apply_** to **education** cannot control how those employers use the information. Applicants should check with specific employer’s privacy policies to ensure the use of information is limited to the purpose of obtaining employment. An applicant can remove his/her application from our searchable database at any time. However, School Boards and Private Employers who have access to our database may have retained a copy of their application in their own files or databases. We are not responsible for the retention, use or privacy of applications in these instances. 

**Use of Cookies**

**_apply_** to **education** uses cookies to help personalize and maximize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on a user’s hard drive by a Web page server. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to your computer, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if a user registers for services, a cookie helps us to recall the specific information (such as user name, password and preferences). Because of our use of cookies, we can deliver faster and more accurate results and a more personalized site experience. When the user returns to the **_apply_** to **education** site, the information the user previously provided can be retrieved. We also use cookies to track click streams and for load balancing. 

Users have the ability to ACCEPT or DECLINE cookies. Most Web browsers automatically ACCEPT cookies, but users can modify their browser setting to DECLINE all cookies if preferred. Alternatively, users may be able to modify the browser setting to notify the user each time a cookie is tendered and permit the user to ACCEPT or DECLINE cookies on an individual basis. If you choose to DECLINE cookies, however, it may hinder performance and negatively impact your experience on the **_apply_** to **education** Web site. 

**Use of Web Beacons**

**_apply_** to **education** Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) that allow us to count users who have visited those pages. Web beacons are not used to access your personally identifiable information on **_apply_** to **education**. They are a technique we use to compile statistics about our Web site usage.

Web beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides.

**Updating Your Information**

Users may review, correct, update or change **_apply_** to **education** account information at any time. Simply log into your **_apply_** to **education** account, review your account information and edit it with the options provided.

**Security**

**_apply_** to **education** has put in place reasonable technical and organizational measures designed to protect your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to overcome those measures and use your personal information for improper purposes.

When you purchase credits online at **_apply_** to **education** , your credit card information is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. SSL makes it difficult for your credit card information to be intercepted while being transmitted. **_apply_** to **education** uses a service company to process its credit card transactions. For further information on this company's privacy and security practices, please [click here](http://www2.eigendev.com/main.html).

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

**_apply_** to **education** reserves the right to modify or supplement this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make any material change to this Privacy Policy, we will update this site to include such changes and notify users for 60 days on the home page of the website. If at any time, you have questions or concerns about **_apply_** to **education** 's Privacy Policy, please feel free to email us at [info@ ** _apply_** to **education**.com](mailto:info@applytoeducation.com) or call our Privacy Officer, Mark Laurie, at 416 932 8866 ext. 222. 

**Contact Information**

**_apply_** to **education** is a division of Passion Inc.; located at 25 Imperial St., Suite 100, Toronto, Ontario, M5P 1B9 

We welcome your comments concerning this Privacy Policy. If you believe we have not adhered to this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [info@ ** _apply_** to **education**.com](mailto:info@applytoeducation.com) or call our Privacy Officer, Mark Laurie, at 416 932 8866 ext. 222. We will do our best to respond to your issue within a reasonable time frame. 

Thank you for using **_apply_** to **education**.

Updated October 16, 2007
